In this world...
Is the destiny of mankind controlled by some transcendental entity or law?
Is it like the hand of God hovering above?
At least it is true...
...that man has no control, even over his own will.
O prince...
O prince of the unforgiven...
We are honored to be received in audience...
We shall meet again in another world...
We are your kin...
Feel no shame about shape
Weather changes their phrase
Even mother will show you another way
So put your glasses on
Nothing will be wrong
There's no blame. There's no fame
It's up to you
The first words should be found
Whatever holds you back
I...
...can...
I can get it off
Tell me what...
Tell me what you want
I don't know why...
Don't know why...
Don't know why you're afraid
Tell me what...
Tell me what you'd say
I don't know why...
Don't know why...
Too late...
It's too late
Infiltration
Are you sure there's a secret
passage in this dismal place?
Our sources are reliable.
If it's so easy to find, then who would
need the help of us mercenaries?
Found it.
I guess we're not needed.
Pippin.
There's no mistake.
This is it.
Right, let's go.
Wait a minute.
I understand that Pippin and
Judeau need to come along...
...but you're the commander now.
Are you sure you should come?
If something were to happen to you...
Our mission is to rescue Griffith.
We have the highest chance to succeed...
...if all four of our strongest
members take on the operation.
Yeah, but...
You're worried, aren't you?
Don't make me laugh!
I'm a stronger swordsman
than either of them.
Don't bring your personal
feelings into this matter.
Obey your commander's orders!
Remember...
...I can still cover your back.
Don't forget that.
Yeah...
Let's go.
Griffith...
You were always looking up to the sky...
To climb higher... To soar higher...
That's all you wanted to do.
You were a hawk flying alone,
reaching for the highest point...
That's right...
You were always watching us from above...
Never here on the ground
with the rest of us...
Calm, cool, and always on the alert.
Do you really need a reason...
...each time I decide to lay
my life on the line for you?
Letting nothing stand
in your path to victory...
Do you find me vile?
Griffith can't go on without you!
If that's true...
If that's the real truth...
Then I...
Pull yourself together.
Griffith will be back soon.
There's no way in hell I'm going to die...
Not without seeing Griffith...
Even if I need a thousand
more stitches in me...
Rickert, we need some more water.
Got it.
When Griffith returns...
It'll be the resurrection
of the Band of the Hawk!
Everyone is in good spirits...
Because Griffith will be back soon...
As long as Griffith comes back, then...
A fairy?
I saw it...
...with my very own eyes.
There's no doubt.
The enemy?
Why now?
Just a little more...
All we needed was a little more time,
and Griffith would be back!
We can't let them destroy us! Not now!
Hey...
Where is everyone?
Run...
Rickert...
It can't...
This can't be real!
What...
What's going on?
I'm amazed we learned
about this secret passage.
We have supporters inside.
Wait.
Supporters of the resistance movement...
You must be the Band of the Hawk.
We are at your service.
The Band of the Hawk's Casca.
What do you mean by supporters?
They're from Princess Charlotte.
Oh...
We don't have very much time until dawn.
We must get to where Griffith's
being kept as soon as possible.
Right.
We'll take it from here.
Darkness... True darkness, where not
a single ray of light can be found.
How long have I been
lying here in this darkness?
An eternity...
...or perhaps a fleeting moment.
I feel nothing...
It's as if my body is floating in space...
I wonder... Have I managed
to preserve my sanity?
Or has it already been lost long ago?
And yet...
...here in this empty, hollow world...
...one thing is clear in my mind.
Him alone...
...like lightning splitting
through the darkness...
He appears in my mind so vividly.
Over and over again like
the waves of a tsunami...
Hatred...
Friendship...
Jealousy...
Frustration...
Helplessness...
Affection...
Sorrow...
They all come together
into a giant vortex...
They pin my fading consciousness
down so that it doesn't slip away.
The one who caused this...
My confinement in this darkness...
Will now...
...become my only chance at survival.
When did it happen? This man,
whose life was once in my hands...
When did I fall into his powerful clutches?
And now...
In my mind I see him radiating
so brightly it pierces my eyes.
Guts!
Griffith?
Is he in a different cell?
No, he has to be here on the lowest level.
Griffith?
Grif...
Gri...
Griffith...
The tendons in his arms
and legs have been slashed...
And his tongue...
Casca, the keys!
Casca!
Stay there!
Stay where you are!
This isn't possible.
This can't be Griffith...
Guts...
Griffith!
There's no escaping now...
The guards and soldiers
will be here any minute...
And in a year, you'll all
be looking just like him...
You bastard...
So you're the bastard
who destroyed his body...
That's right.
I haven't had that
much fun in a long time.
You don't come across a specimen
as splendid as him very often.
When you're as experienced as
I am in the profession of torture...
...not only do you appreciate
the beauty that's on the surface...
...but also the beauty beneath the skin,
in the tendons, muscles, and veins.
He really was exquisite.
It's no use.
This door is four times
thicker than your average door.
Don't move!
Put down your weapons and surrender!
Stick with me and don't fall back!
Guts!
How dare you?
What the hell are you all doing?
Shoot them!
You idiots!
Who said to retreat?
Hold your ground!
Hurry!
What's taking them so long?
There are thirty of our soldiers
against just the four of them!
How can it be so difficult?
Yes, but, sir...
...they're led by that man,
the hundred-man slayer!
Don't be stupid!
How can we be sure that their
raider commander himself is here?
No...
Besides, myths like that
are born in times of war...
...when stories get exaggerated.
There is no man in the world who
can slay a hundred armed soldiers.
Maybe ten soldiers at the very most.
That is definitely him...
The Band of the Hawk's
ruthless commander...
Guts!
It's Hundred-Man Guts himself!
Surround him!
What are you waiting for?
Seize him!
But, sir...
You idiots!
He's been waving his huge sword
around while chasing after our men...
He's out of breath.
You fools!
If your enemy sees you hesitating,
you've already lost the battle.
Put your lives on the line and
see how ruthless the battlefield is!
Guts!
Advance!
Where are they?
See, it was too much
for just the four of them...
No...
You're wrong. They'll be back.
I'm sure of it.
Guts...
What a disgrace!
If we let them get away,
the king will never forgive us.
Pursue them!
We're going to head them off
and then ambush them!
Yes, sir!
Looking back, the morning comes.
Don't find your face in your glass.
Take the moonlight by the tail.
It's a rainy sight. You're shading.
What is that?
It's just the same.
What is trying your crown?
I'm spending my glass, walking back.
So wear my glass. You're fading.
I'm waiting so long.
I'm waiting...